<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Port Harcourt Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- Category name for restaurant [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_restaurant">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for churches [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_churches">Churches</string>

    <!-- Category name for hotels [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_hotel">Hotels</string>

    <!-- Category name for coys [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_companies">Companies</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <!-- Below are the string resources for the restaurant and about them -->
    <string name="spice_route">Spice Route</string>
    <string name="about_spice_route">If you love Indian food, this is the place to be,
        it is also a hub for those Friday nights rendezvous. Spice is the new spot in Port-Harcourt
        city. Also, when you visit take time to look at Buddha’s statue.
        Located at, No 1 Azikiwe Road, shop 36/37 Port Harcourt Mall. \nPure passion coupled with a
        drive to succeed and an unquenching thirst for authentic and flavorful Indian food led to
        the creation of the brand.
    </string>

    <string name="asian_town">Asian Town</string>
    <string name="about_asian_town">Port-Harcourt has always played home to some of the best
        Chinese cuisine, but this beats standards set before its arrival, a serene and cool
        place to have lunch, dinner, even to throw that Dinner party. Personal Recommendation;
        Sunday Brunch is always lit, you should try it. Located at No 24 Forces Avenue, Old GRA,
        Port-Harcourt.
    </string>

    <string name="charcoal">Charcoal and Spice</string>
    <string name="about_charcoal">
        Located at the heart of GRA, Charcoal and spice is a place to
        have that brunch after a busy half day, the serenity of this place is second to none,
        so if you imagine having that lush taste of good food in your mouth while you sit in a
        beautiful garden, you can find them at King Perekule street, GRA phase 2. Don’t worry,
        you can’t miss it.
    </string>

    <string name="cravings">Cravings</string>
    <string name="about_cravings">Port Harcourt’s finest dining restaurant, if you have in mind
        to meet the Porsche young folks in the city or maybe you want to have a good time with a
        friend or even alone, this is your joint. The food alone speaks volumes, you should try it
        out. Located at, 20 Elelenwo street, GRA Phase 2, Port Harcourt.
    </string>

    <string name="salvation">Salvation Ministries</string>
    <string name="about_salvation">Salvation Ministries started on the 13th of April 1997 at
        plot 35 Birabi Street GRA 1 Port Harcourt with 34 members: 15 males, 10 females and 9
        children in attendance. \nToday, she has become a church with an over-flowing crowd in her
        headquarters presently located at plot 17 Birabi Street GRA 1 Port Harcourt, her satellite
        churches and on the internet. Salvation Ministries has increased from one Sunday service to
        five power-packed Sunday services.
    </string>

    <string name="tka">The King\'s Assembly</string>
    <string name="about_tka">Started first service on Sunday, 3rd of October 2004 at
        Aladumo Miracle Hall, Aba Road, Port Harcourt. The Ministry has since grown to our
        present location at 1, Stadium Road, By Airforce Junction, Port Harcourt, Nigeria
        and our first international mission centre office in South Africa.
    </string>

    <string name="hotr">House on the Rock, Port Harcourt</string>
    <string name="about_hotr">House on the Rock, Port Harcourt is a parish of House on the Rock
        church; one of the fastest growing churches in Nigeria. \nIn December 1994, with a vision of
        empowering believers to fulfil their God ordained destinies, the church under the leadership
        of Pastor Paul Adeolu Adefarasin started with a Friday night prayer meeting with seven (7)
        people in attendance. From this humble beginning, the church family has now become
        multi-racial and multi-faceted with over seven thousand (7, 000) people in attendance in the
        headquater church, which holds its services at the Muson Center in Lagos, Nigeria. \nSince
        1994, over 50 branches of the church family have been birth in Europe and Africa.
        House on theRock, Port Harcourt was birth in May 2000 and serves as a paradigm for
        cutting-edge ministry in the city of Port Harcourt and its environs.
    </string>

    <string name="jesus_house">RCCG, Jesus House Parish</string>
    <string name="about_jesus_house">RCCG Jesus House PHC is where Jesus lives!! Come and you will
        meet Him. It is with great joy that we welcome you to JESUS HOUSE, PHC.
    </string>

    <string name="phrc">The Port Harcourt Refining Company, PHRC.</string>
    <string name="about_phrc">PHRC is a Nigeria-based oil and gas company primarily specializing in
        the refining of crude oil into petroleum products. It is headquartered in Port Harcourt
        metropolitan area of Rivers State, southeastern Nigeria. The company is a subsidiary of the
        Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC).\nLocated in Alesa Eleme just to the southeast
        of Port Harcourt, the company operates two oil refineries, including an old plant
        commissioned in 1965 that can process 60,000
        barrels of oil per stream day (bpsd), as well as the new plant commissioned in 1989,
        which has a capacity of 150,000 bpsd. Both oil refineries possess a combined capacity of
        210,000 barrels per stream day making PHRC the "biggest oil refining company in Nigeria"
    </string>

    <string name="epcl">Eleme Petrochemicals Company Limited (EPCL)</string>
    <string name="about_epcl">Located in Port Harcourt, Rivers State, is a petrochemicals complex
        originally fully-owned by the Federal Government of Nigeria and commissioned in 1996.
        Although constructed to international standards, located to take advantage of Nigeria’s
        abundant supplies of natural gas, and designed to manufacture products for which there was
        consistently high demand. \nIn 2006, EPCL was privatised by the sale of 75% of its shares to a core investor through
        a competitive bidding process. Little international interest was attracted. The company
        was sold to Indorama Group without liabilities which were retained by the FGN. The company
        was handed over on October 26, 2006. \nIndorama immediately embarked upon a $130 million turnaround maintenance and capital
        investment programme, returning the facility to operating condition within four months.
        Its production output quickly surpassed pre-privatisation levels. EPCL immediately returned
        to profitability, buoyed by rising world prices for the polyolefins it produced.
    </string>

    <string name="nlng">Nigeria LNG Limited</string>
    <string name="about_nlng">Nigeria LNG Limited was incorporated as a limited liability company
        on May 17, 1989 to harness Nigeria\'s vast natural gas resources and produce Liquefied
        Natural Gas (LNG) and Natural Gas Liquids (NGLs) for export.\nThe company is owned by four shareholders, namely, the Federal Government of Nigeria,
        represented by Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (49%); Shell (25.6%);
        Total Gaz Electricite Holdings France​ (15%) and Eni (10.4%).\nWith six trains currently operational, NLNG\'s plant, on Bonny Island in Rivers State,
        is capable of producing 22 Million Tonnes Per Annum (MTPA) of LNG, and 5 MTPA of NGLs
        (LPG and Condensate) from 3.5 Billion (standard) cubic feet per day (Bcf/d) of natural gas
        intake. NLNG\'s near term expansion plans include construction of a seventh train to
        complement the existing six train structure, which when in operation will up the company\'s
        total production capacity to 30 million tonnes per annum (MTPA) of LNG.
​ </string>

    <string name="shell">Shell Producing and Development Company</string>
    <string name="about_shell">Shell has been active in Nigeria since 1937.  Shell companies and
        investments have played a pioneering role in onshore, shallow and deep water oil exploration
        and production. Shell has also been at the forefront of gas development, producing and
        delivering gas to domestic consumers and export markets for over 40 years. \nThe Shell Petroleum Development Company of Nigeria Limited (SPDC) is the largest Shell
        company in Nigeria and produced the country’s first commercial oil exports in 1958. SPDC
        is the operator of a joint venture (the SPDC JV) between the government-owned Nigerian
        National Petroleum Corporation – NNPC (55% share), SPDC (30%), Total E and P Nigeria Ltd (10%)
        and the ENI subsidiary Agip Oil Company Limited (5%). It is focused on onshore and shallow
        water oil and gas production in the Niger Delta.
    </string>

    <string name="presidential">Hotel Presidential</string>
    <string name="about_presidential">Hotel Presidential – managed by Courdeau Nigeria Limited –
        is located in the heart of the Garden City - Port Harcourt, \'the Capital of Rivers State\',
        Nigeria, and less than an hour drive from the International and Domestic Airport.
        Being centrally situated within the business districts and the main shopping areas of the
        city, Hotel Presidential is an ideal choice for both leisure and business travelers. \nThe
        hotel\'s 5-Star status is reflected through its 241 tastefully furnished Rooms and 53
        spacious Suites, in addition to several banquet halls that can definitely meet your
        expectations. 24-Hour concierge, room service and laundry available. To ease your stress,
        you can play tennis in one of our two courts with your partners or our coach, visit our
        gymnasium that is open from 6am till 10pm, or even swim in our 33meter outdoor pool,
        which makes your stay even more enjoyable.
    </string>

    <string name="novotel">Novotel</string>
    <string name="about_novotel">
        Novotel Port Harcourt offers the perfect blend of comfort and convenience for your
        visit to the Garden City. Its location is ideal for both leisure and business travelers
        conveniently situated only 20 minutes from the Airport and golf course. Our rooms are
        spaciously designed to suit every traveling style or requirement. Facilities include
        restaurant, bar, laundry service, pool, parking and fitness center. Venues accommodate up
        to 340 delegates with flexible packages available to suite your convenience.\nNovotel Port
        Harcourt is located at 3 Stadium Road Rumuomasi,
        3.9 miles from the center of Port Harcourt. Liberation Stadium is the closest landmark to
        Novotel Port Harcourt.
    </string>

    <string name="laking">LA King Hotel</string>
    <string name="about_laking">A stay at L.A Kings Hotel places you in the heart of Port Harcourt,
        a 3-minute drive from Liberation Stadium and 9 minutes from Sharks Stadium.
        Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services,
        and a 24-hour front desk. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge,
        and free self parking is available onsite.
    </string>

    <string name="golden">Golden Tulip, Port Harcourt</string>
    <string name="about_golden">A stay at Golden Tulip Port Harcourt places you in the heart of
        Port Harcourt, a 4-minute drive from Liberation Stadium and 7 minutes from Sharks Stadium.
        Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby,
        and dry cleaning/laundry services. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a
        surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.
    </string>

    <string name="web_resource"> Web Resource </string>
    <string name="web_presidential">https://www.presidential-hotel.com/</string>
    <string name="web_novotel">https://www.kayak.com/Port-Harcourt-Hotels-Novotel-Port-Harcourt.59057.ksp</string>
    <string name="web_laking">https://www.kayak.com/Port-Harcourt-Hotels-L-A-Kings-Hotel.3126543.ksp</string>
    <string name="web_golden">https://www.kayak.com/Port-Harcourt-Hotels-Golden-Tulip-Port-Harcourt.645609.ksp#description</string>
    <string name="web_nlng">http://www.nlng.com/Careers/Pages/Home.aspx</string>
    <string name="web_phrc">https://www.nnpcgroup.com/Refining/Pages/PHRC.aspx</string>
    <string name="web_shell">https://www.shell.com.ng/</string>
    <string name="web_epcl">https://www.indoramaeleme.com/</string>
    <string name="web_hotr">https://houseontherock.org.ng/</string>
    <string name="web_tka">https://www.thekingsassembly.org/</string>
    <string name="web_salvation">https://smhos.org/</string>
    <string name="web_jesus_house">http://www.rccgjesushousephc.org/</string>
    <string name="web_craving">https://ofadaa.com/port-harcourt/restaurants/cravings-restaurant-cafe</string>
    <string name="web_charcoal">https://ofadaa.com/port-harcourt/restaurants/charcoal-spice-restaurant</string>
    <string name="web_asian">https://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurant_Review-g298363-d4894337-Reviews-AsiaTown-Port_Harcourt_Rivers_State.html</string>
    <string name="web_spice_route">http://spicerouterestaurants.com/about-us</string>



</resources>
